The SCOAN Sunday Service
Now, let’s look for peace – the little you have will be sufficient.
Tell your neighbour, “Look for peace – peace of heart – the little you have will be sufficient”.
Without peace, if you have the whole world, you are in trouble.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour once again, “Look for peace – peace of heart – the little, the atom you have will be sufficient”.
Without the peace of heart, if you have the whole world, you will have trouble.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That will be the summary of my message.
When you wake up in the morning, you are looking, you want to be great, rich - you are looking for money,
business - you are ready to do anything to get it.
Anything to get it cannot give you a peace of heart.
The only thing that will give you peace of heart is to consider your neighbour
while looking for your own.
Tell your neighbour:
“The only thing that will give you peace of heart is to consider your neighbour
while looking for your way out”.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you don’t consider your neighbour while looking for the way out of your problem,
you have not considered Jesus, your Creator.
Remember, your neighbour can be someone who does not share the same faith with you.
Once again,
the only way you can have that peace of heart is to always consider your neighbour,
while searching for the way out.
Your neighbour can be someone who does not share the same faith with you.
Your neighbour can be your enemy.
Your neighbour can be your friend.
While looking for the way out of your mess, difficulties, whatever situation you have;
when you are looking for a way, "How will I get this business done? I'm poor. I want to apply for a business.",
consider your neighbour.
What has happened to your neighbour?
If your neighbour is entitled to the same business, and you want to take it by any mean -
you want to do anything to take that business,
and you know your neighbour is the best for that business, but you have a way of taking it,
you continue to take it - no peace of heart.
Write it down.
While looking for a way out, always consider your neighbour.
Your neighbour can be your friend, your enemy, can be those who do not share the same faith with you -
consider them!
Do you know the reason why you have to consider your neighbour,
those who do not share the same faith with you?
Your enemy today may be your saviour tomorrow.
It may be the one to take you to the promised land - your greatest enemy today.
Your greatest enemy, that wants you to die, that is after your life, is the number one enemy today,
may be your saviour any moment from now,
and will be the one to take you to the promised land.
I take it back again.
While looking for a way out, consider your neighbour.
What does that mean?
Wish your neighbour as you wish yourself.
Stop that your prayer; you want to kill your enemy...
If you say you want to kill your enemy...
You know, you were once an enemy to someone else before, and you were not killed.
But today, you want to kill your enemy.
And that person who is your enemy - he wants to kill you in the same way you want to kill him.
You are wasting your time, killing your enemy, when the Lord said,
"I will set a table before you, in the presence of your enemy".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are wasting your time.
Because the Lord said, "I will set a table before you, in the presence of your who"?
If you have killed them, who will be there to see your goodness?
Who will testify to your goodness?
Look at you - 99% of people today were once my enemies who wanted to kill me.
You were fasting, praying, binding me and loosing at the same time.
In the past, 90% of people sitting here today;
anytime they saw Emmanuel TV, "Please! Switch it off. Over my dead body, I will come to that church.",
but your real body is here today, because you are not killed.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Because you are not killed...
Don't waste your time - I don't waste my time, because I know where I'm going.
Because we don't know where we are going.
If you knew where you are going, you will not waste your time over your enemy;
no enemy can stop you from where you are going.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Because you believe they can stop you, that is why you want to stop them - no!
Do and let me do - your life is just...
Please; there are many things we need to know that will guide us.
When you want to pray, ask for God's mercy and His favour, and thank Him,
and let Him know that here you are.
If you want someone, He should send you and leave that prayer.
Stop wasting your time over your enemy.
For how long?
I want to leave you - please, take this message.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 14/08/2018 RV: Esther Mwelwa 14/08/2018